Guide to the John Vliet Lindsay Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- New York City Mayoral Personal Papers, 1965-1973; Part II
  - Speech Files, 1966-1969; Series V
    - The Lotos Club, 1966 November 28 (Box 65, Folder 244)
    - Joint committee for promotion of the Port of New York, 1966 November 30 (Box 65, Folder 245)
    - American Whig - Cliosophic Society, Princeton, 1966 November 30 (Box 65, Folder 246)
    - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, 1966 December 1 (Box 65, Folder 247)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust Co., 1966 December 2 (Box 65, Folder 248)
    - Dwight Inn of Phi Delta Phi, New York Law School, 1966 December 3 (Box 65, Folder 249)
    - Health Research Council, 1966 December 5 (Box 65, Folder 250)
    - New York University, School of Commerce, 1966 December 5 (Box 65, Folder 251)
    - United Neighboord Houses of New York, 1966 December 6 (Box 65, Folder 252)
    - Volunteer Coordinating Council, 1966 December 7 (Box 65, Folder 253)
    - U. S. O. and New York City National Shrenes Associates, 1966 December 7 (Box 65, Folder 254)
    - LaGuardia Memorial, 1966 December 10 (Box 65, Folder 255)
    - City Athletic Club, 1966 December 3 (Box 65, Folder 256)
    - International Rescue Committee, 1966 December 13 (Box 65, Folder 257)
    - Christmas tree lighting, 1966 December 15 (Box 65, Folder 258)
    - Pace College, 1966 December 19 (Box 65, Folder 259)
    - Joint Legislative Committee on Metropolitan and Regional Areas Study, 1966 December 20 (Box 65, Folder 260)
    - Conference on Air Pollution Control, testimony, 1967 January 4 (Box 66, Folder 261)
    - Sears Roebuck and Company, 1967 January 5 (Box 66, Folder 262)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, 1967 January 5 (Box 66, Folder 263)
    - Clarion Concert Committee for Italian flood relief, 1967 January 6 (Box 66, Folder 264)
    - The Sperry and Hutchinson Co. (cancelled), 1967 January 6 (Box 66, Folder 265)
    - Northeast Queens Council for Schools, 1967 January 7 (Box 66, Folder 266)
    - The New York Couture Business Council, Inc., 1967 January 8 (Box 66, Folder 267)
    - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies of New York, 1967 January 9 (Box 66, Folder 268)
    - New York Shakespeare Festival, 1967 January 10 (Box 66, Folder 269)
    - General Theological Seminary, Alumni Association, 1967 January 11 (Box 66, Folder 270)
    - Bronx County Bar Assoication, 1967 January 11 (Box 66, Folder 271)
    - New York State Chamber of Commerce executives, 1967 January 12 (Box 66, Folder 272)
    - Science and Technology Council to the Mayor, 1967 January 12 (Box 66, Folder 273)
    - Organization and Urban Responsibility, 1967 January 12 (Box 66, Folder 274)
    - National Association of Engine and Boat Manufacturers, 1967 January 14 (Box 66, Folder 275)
    - United Parents Associations of New York City, 1967 January 14 (Box 66, Folder 276)
    - New York Consumer Assembly, 1967 January 14 (Box 66, Folder 277)
    - New York Jaycees, 1967 January 17 (Box 66, Folder 278)
    - Friends of the City Center, 1967 January 17 (Box 66, Folder 279)
    - Union League Club of N. Y., 1967 January 18 (Box 66, Folder 280)
    - Outstanding public housing tenants, awards ceremony, 1967 January 18 (Box 66, Folder 281)
    - New York City Housing Authority, 1967 January 18 (Box 66, Folder 282)
    - Greater New York Hospital Association, 1967 January 19 (Box 66, Folder 283)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Social Service and Children's Aid Society, 1967 January 19 (Box 66, Folder 284)
    - Housing Police Superior Officers Association, 1967 January 21 (Box 66, Folder 285)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1967 January 23 (Box 66, Folder 286)
    - City Center of Music and Drama, 1967 January 23 (Box 67, Folder 287)
    - New School for Social Research, 1967 January 23 (Box 67, Folder 288)
    - John V. Lindsay Republican Association of Queens, 1967 January 23 (Box 67, Folder 289)
    - Board of Education of the City of New York, 1967 January 24 (Box 67, Folder 290)
    - Responsive environment program of the Board of Education, 1967 January 24 (Box 67, Folder 291)
    - Columbia University, 1967 January 25 (Box 67, Folder 292)
    - The Pilgrims of the United States, 1967 January 25 (Box 67, Folder 293)
    - City Council of Reorganization, 1967 January 26 (Box 67, Folder 294-295)
    - The Cathedral Club, 1967 January 26 (Box 67, Folder 296)
    - Association of Judges of Family Court of the State of New York, 1967 January 26 (Box 67, Folder 297)
    - New York State Bar Association (Rankin), 1967 January 27 (Box 67, Folder 298)
    - The Women's National Republican Club, 1967 January 28 (Box 67, Folder 299)
    - The New York Film Critics, 1967 January 29 (Box 67, Folder 300)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1967 January 31 (Box 67, Folder 301)
    - The United States Jaycees (cancelled), 1967 February 1 (Box 67, Folder 302)
    - Joint Legislative Committee on Housing and Development, 1967 February 2 (Box 67, Folder 303)
    - Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 1967 February 2 (Box 67, Folder 304)
    - Memorial services for the three astronauts, 1967 February 3 (Box 67, Folder 305)
    - New York State Society of Newspaper Editors, 1967 February 6 (Box 67, Folder 306)
    - The Association of Towns of the State of New York, 1967 February 6 (Box 67, Folder 307)
    - Fellowship Commission, 1967 February 6 (Box 67, Folder 308)
    - Junior High School 61, Queens, 1967 February 8 (Box 67, Folder 309)
    - Task Force on Environmental Health and Related Problems, 1967 February 10 (Box 67, Folder 310)
    - Kings County Republican Committee, 1967 February 11 (Box 67, Folder 311)
    - Republican County Committee of the County of New York, 1967 February 11 (Box 67, Folder 312)
    - American Judicature Society, 1967 February 13 (Box 67, Folder 313)
    - Herald Tribune Fresh Air Fund, 1967 February 14 (Box 67, Folder 314)
    - New York Board of Trade, 1967 February 14 (Box 67, Folder 315)
    - Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry (TAPPI), 1967 February 15 (Box 67, Folder 316)
    - Testimony on proposed state budget for the 1967-1968 fiscal year, 1967 February 16 (Box 68, Folder 317)
    - WNYC-TV, Spanish Language Program, 1967 February 17 (Box 68, Folder 318)
    - John V. Lindsay Republican Organization of Queens, 1967 February 17 (Box 68, Folder 319)
    - Television message to tourists, Channel 6, 1967 February 21 (Box 68, Folder 320)
    - Propeller Club of the United States, 1967 February 23 (Box 68, Folder 321)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Chamber of Commerce, 1967 February 24 (Box 68, Folder 322)
    - Career Civil Service Awards, 1967 February 24 (Box 68, Folder 323)
    - International Union of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, 1967 February 25 (Box 68, Folder 324)
    - Department of Welfare, 1967 February 28 (Box 68, Folder 325)
    - Mayor's Medal, 1967 February 28 (Box 68, Folder 326)
    - West Side Chamber of Commerce of the City of New York, 1967 February 28 (Box 68, Folder 327)
    - U. S. News and World Report, editorial board interview (Washington), 1967 March 1 (Box 68, Folder 328)
    - International Flower Show, 1967 March 4 (Box 68, Folder 329)
    - Reform Independent Democrats of Fifth Assembly District South, 1967 March 6 (Box 68, Folder 330)
    - Ramar Industries, Inc., 1967 March 6 (Box 68, Folder 331)
    - Liberal Party of New York State, 1967 March 8 (Box 68, Folder 332)
    - New Haven Advertising Club, 1967 March 9 (Box 68, Folder 333)
    - Yale Law Forum, 1967 March 10 (Box 68, Folder 334)
    - Film Producers Association of New York, Inc., 1967 March 11 (Box 68, Folder 335)
    - New York Association for Brain Injured Children, 1967 March 12 (Box 68, Folder 336)
    - Holy Name Society of the Police Department, 1967 March 12 (Box 68, Folder 337)
    - Concert Artists Guild, Inc., 1967 March 12 (Box 68, Folder 338)
    - Tilyou Theatre Open House Town Hall Forum, 1967 March 13 (Box 68, Folder 339)
    - Citizens Budget Commission, 1967 March 14 (Box 69, Folder 340)
    - Police Academy, Recruit Training School, commencement exercises, 1967 March 15 (Box 69, Folder 341)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare, 1967 March 15 (Box 69, Folder 342)
    - Weekly radio broadcasts (1967 Mar 17-Nov 3), 1967 March 17 (Box 69, Folder 343)
    - Society of the Friendly Sons of Saint Patrick, 1967 March 17 (Box 69, Folder 344)
    - Testimony on the Regional Transportation Legislation, 1967 March 22 (Box 69, Folder 345)
    - Antoinette Perry Awards Program, 1967 March 26 (Box 69, Folder 346)
    - Dance Magazine (Heckscher), 1967 March 27 (Box 69, Folder 347)
    - New York Young Republican Club, 1967 March 31 (Box 69, Folder 348)
    - Testimony before the House Judiciary Committee, 1967 April 5 (Box 69, Folder 349)
    - Testimony before the Senate Commerce Committee, 1967 April 5 (Box 69, Folder 350)
    - Manhattan School of Musuc (Heckscher), 1967 April 5 (Box 69, Folder 351)
    - Francis Lewis Democratic Club (cancelled), 1967 April 8 (Box 69, Folder 352)
    - New School of Social Research, television program, 1967 April 10 (Box 69, Folder 353)
    - New York City Builders' Association, 1967 April 10 (Box 69, Folder 354)
    - George T. Delacorte New York Shakespeare Festival, 1967 April 10 (Box 69, Folder 355)
    - John Jay College of Criminal Justice, 1967 April 11 (Box 69, Folder 356)
    - Young Men's Christian Association, 1967 April 11 (Box 69, Folder 357)
    - Public School 312 (Eugene Hult), 1967 April 12 (Box 69, Folder 358)
    - "Instant Rehabilitation", re: the East 5th Street Rehabilitation Experiment, 1967 April 13 (Box 69, Folder 359)
    - Pier 60: United States Lines, 1967 April 13 (Box 69, Folder 360)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1967 April 13 (Box 69, Folder 361)
    - 66th Assembly District Republican Organization, 1967 April 14 (Box 69, Folder 362)
    - Brooklyn Women's Division of the American Committee on Italian Immigration, 1967 April 15 (Box 69, Folder 363)
    - Puerto Rican Community Conference, 1967 April 15 (Box 69, Folder 364)
    - New York Tuberculosis and Health Association, 1967 April 18 (Box 69, Folder 365)
    - Small Business Chamber of Commerce (cancelled), 1967 April 19 (Box 69, Folder 366)
    - Westinghouse Broadcasting Company, Inc. (cancelled), 1967 April 19 (Box 69, Folder 367)
    - American Society of Newspaper Editors, 1967 April 20 (Box 69, Folder 368)
    - Building Trades Employer's Association, 1967 April 20 (Box 69, Folder 369)
    - Drama Desk, 1967 April 21 (Box 69, Folder 370)
    - Pelham Parkway Republican Club, 1967 April 21 (Box 69, Folder 371)
    - West Brooklyn Civic Improvement Council, 1967 April 21 (Box 69, Folder 372)
    - March of Dimes "Man of the Year" Award Dinner (Johnny Carson), 1967 April 23 (Box 69, Folder 373)
    - Institute of Politics, Harvard University, 1967 April 23-24 (Box 69, Folder 374)
    - American Newspaper Publishers Association, 1967 April 26 (Box 69, Folder 375)
    - Association of Women's Committees for Symphony Orchestras, 1967 April 26 (Box 69, Folder 376)
    - Avenue of the Americas Association, Inc., 1967 April 27 (Box 69, Folder 377)
    - Board of National Missions of the United Presbyterian Church of the United States of America, 1967 April 27 (Box 69, Folder 378)
    - Public Education Association, 1967 April 27 (Box 70, Folder 379)
    - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, 1967 April 28 (Box 70, Folder 380)
    - Brooklyn Council, Kings County, Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1967 April 29 (Box 70, Folder 381)
    - New York County Council, Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1967 April 29 (Box 70, Folder 382)
    - WCBS-TV Career Fair, 1967 May 1 (Box 70, Folder 383)
    - New York Botanical Garden, 1967 May 1 (Box 70, Folder 384)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1967 May 1 (Box 70, Folder 385)
    - Magazine Advertising Club of New York, 1967 May 2 (Box 70, Folder 386)
    - Department of Corrections pre-release program, 1967 May 3 (Box 70, Folder 387)
    - Masaryk Towers, 1967 May 3 (Box 70, Folder 388)
    - The City Club, 1967 May 3 (Box 70, Folder 389)
    - American Musical and Dramatic Academy, The National Hemophilia Foundation, 1967 May 3 (Box 70, Folder 390)
    - Narcotics Control Act, city/state signing, 1967 May 4 (Box 70, Folder 391)
    - Columbus Park Towers, 1967 May 4 (Box 70, Folder 392)
    - Citizens' Committee to keep New York Clean, 1967 May 4 (Box 70, Folder 393)
    - New York Urban League, 1967 May 5 (Box 70, Folder 394)
    - Paper Merchants Association of New York, 1967 May 4 (Box 70, Folder 395)
    - King's County Council of Jewish War Veterans, 1967 May 7 (Box 70, Folder 396)
    - Zionist Organization of America, 1967 May 7 (Box 70, Folder 397)
    - Young Men's and Young Women's Hebreu Association, 1967 May 5 (Box 70, Folder 398)
    - Kings County Liberal Party, 1967 May 7 (Box 70, Folder 399)
    - National League for Nursing, Inc., 1967 May 8 (Box 70, Folder 400)
    - Testimony before Senate Subcommittee on Manpower, Employment and Poverty (Box 70, Folder 401)
    - Day Care Council of New York, 1967 May 8 (Box 70, Folder 402)
    - Association for Mentally Ill Children, 1967 May 8 (Box 70, Folder 403)
    - National Association of Business Economists, 1967 May 9 (Box 70, Folder 404)
    - Citizen's Committee for children of New York, Inc., 1967 May 10 (Box 70, Folder 405)
    - The American Bankers Association, 1967 May 10 (Box 70, Folder 406)
    - Salute to Spring, 1967 May 10 (Box 70, Folder 407)
    - The mayor's prayer breakfast, New York City Citizens' Committee (cancelled), 1967 May 11 (Box 70, Folder 408)
    - Citizens' Union of the City of New York, 1967 May 11 (Box 70, Folder 409-410)
    - Adoptive parents annual party, 1967 May 11 (Box 70, Folder 411)
    - Greater Syracuse Chamber of Commerce, 1967 May 12 (Box 70, Folder 412)
    - "Design-In" conference, 1967 May 13 (Box 70, Folder 413)
    - National police conference on P.A.L. and youth activities, 1967 May 15 (Box 70, Folder 414)
    - Bankers Trust Company, 1967 May 16 (Box 70, Folder 415)
    - League of Womens Voters, 1967 May 16 (Box 70, Folder 416)
    - Department of Markets, New York City terminal market, Hunts Point, 1967 May 17 (Box 70, Folder 417)
    - New York Stock Exchange, 1967 May 17 (Box 70, Folder 418)
    - The American Institute of Architects, 1967 May 17 (Box 70, Folder 419)
    - Junior High School 74, Queens (walking tour), 1967 May 18 (Box 70, Folder 420)
    - Queens Junior High School, 1967 May 18 (Box 70, Folder 421)
    - Brooklyn Psychiatric Centers, Inc., 1967 May 18 (Box 70, Folder 422)
    - Pennsylvania Society of newspaper Editors, 1967 May 19 (Box 71, Folder 423)
    - Encampment for Citizenship, 1967 May 23 (Box 71, Folder 424)
    - Theater Arts Center, 1967 May 24 (Box 71, Folder 425)
    - Adventure playground, 1967 May 25 (Box 71, Folder 426)
    - National Fathers' Day committee, 1967 May 25 (Box 71, Folder 427)
    - Special Libraries Association, 1967 May 29 (Box 71, Folder 428)
    - National Cartoonist Society, 1967 May 31 (Box 71, Folder 429)
    - Metropolitan Regional Council, 1967 June 1 (Box 71, Folder 430)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce, 1967 June 1 (Box 71, Folder 431)
    - Puerto Rican Parade Committee, 1967 June 2 (Box 71, Folder 432)
    - Flushing Meadow Carona Park, 1967 June 3 (Box 71, Folder 433)
    - John Jay College of Criminal Justice, 1967 June 4 (Box 71, Folder 434)
    - Contello Towers, 1967 June 5 (Box 71, Folder 435)
    - Fire Department of the City of New York, 1967 June 5 (Box 71, Folder 436)
    - New York City Central Labor Council rally for Israel, 1967 June 5 (Box 71, Folder 437)
    - New York Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1967 June 6 (Box 71, Folder 438)
    - The Presbytery of New York City, 1967 June 6 (Box 71, Folder 439)
    - Columbia University - Presbyterian Hospital, 1967 June 6 (Box 71, Folder 440)
    - Public Affairs Council, 1967 June 7 (Box 71, Folder 441)
    - Parent Teachers' Association P.S. 171, 1967 June 7 (Box 71, Folder 442)
    - New York State Republican Committee, 1967 June 8 (Box 71, Folder 443)
    - New York Civil Service Employees Committee for Histadrut (cancelled), 1967 June 10 (Box 71, Folder 444)
    - Village East Towers, 1967 June 10 (Box 71, Folder 445)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Centers, 1967 June 10 (Box 71, Folder 446)
    - Berriman Junior High School, 1967 June 26 (Box 71, Folder 447)
    - Nathanial Hawthorne Jr. High School, 1967 June 26 (Box 71, Folder 448)
    - New York City Commission to United Nations, 1967 June 27 (Box 71, Folder 449)
    - Republican County Committee of the County of New York, 1967 June 27 (Box 71, Folder 450)
    - Police Department, medal day ceremonies, 1967 June 28 (Box 71, Folder 451)
    - Benjamin Franklin High School, 1967 June 29 (Box 71, Folder 452)
    - Uptown Chamber of Commerce, 1967 June 30 (Box 71, Folder 453)
    - New York City Ballet and Opera Company (Montreal cancelled), 1967 July 2 (Box 71, Folder 454)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank Foundation, 1967 July 5 (Box 71, Folder 455)
    - Professional trainee Program, 1967 July 5 (Box 71, Folder 456)
    - Tape: "Youth Wants to Know" WNYE-TV, 1967 July 6 (Box 71, Folder 457)
    - Anti-crime and anti-narcotic committee of upper Park Avenue Baptist church, 1967 July 7 (Box 71, Folder 458)
    - Project Diadem - Return (Institute for Crippled and Disabled), 1967 July 7 (Box 71, Folder 459)
    - Mayors of the Conference of Metropolitan Cities of New York State, 1967 July 11 (Box 71, Folder 460)
    - Project Cadence ceremonies, 1967 July 17 (Box 71, Folder 461)
    - New York Philharmonic, 1967 July 18 (Box 71, Folder 462)
    - New York City housing police, 1967 July 19 (Box 71, Folder 463)
    - American Field Service International Scholarships, 1967 July 21 (Box 71, Folder 464)
    - Parks Department, dedication of "Moses" Platz, 1967 July 21 (Box 71, Folder 465)
    - Newtown Creek water pollution Control plant, 1967 July 24 (Box 71, Folder 466)
    - The National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1967 July 24 (Box 71, Folder 467)
    - National League of Cities, 1967 July 31 (Box 71, Folder 468)
    - National League of Cities, 1967 July 31 (Box 72, Folder 469)
    - Large city boards of education meeting with Govenor Ernor Rockefeller, 1967 August 8 (Box 72, Folder 470)
    - Medals of honor broadcast, WNEW, 1967 August 9 (Box 72, Folder 471)
    - Constitutional convention statement, 1967 August 13 (Box 72, Folder 472)
    - Police promotion ceremony, 1967 August 17 (Box 72, Folder 473)
    - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, district No. 8, 1967 August 21 (Box 72, Folder 474)
    - National Coalition, 1967 August 24 (Box 72, Folder 475)
    - New York Transportation Center, 1967 August 28 (Box 72, Folder 476)
    - New York City Urban Corps, 1967 August 28 (Box 72, Folder 477)
    - Commission on urban problems, 1967 September 7 (Box 72, Folder 478)
    - Sanitation Department, promotion ceremonies, 1967 September 8 (Box 72, Folder 479)
    - Franklin Stores, 1967 September 11 (Box 72, Folder 480)
    - Senate Finance Committee, 1967 amendments to the Social Security Act, 1967 September 12 (Box 72, Folder 481)
    - New York Stock Exchange, 1967 September 13 (Box 72, Folder 482)
    - Council of state chambers of commerce (cancelled), 1967 September 14 (Box 72, Folder 483)
    - "100 Women of Accomplishment," Harper's Bazaar, 1967 September 15 (Box 72, Folder 484)
    - New York Press Association, 1967 September 16 (Box 72, Folder 485)
    - Commerce and Industry Association, 1967 September 18 (Box 72, Folder 486)
    - Big Brothers, Inc., 1967 September 18 (Box 72, Folder 487)
    - The Children's Aid Society (cancelled), 1967 September 20 (Box 72, Folder 488)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 1967 September 20 (Box 72, Folder 489)
    - Richmond County Civic Improvement Association, 1967 September 22 (Box 72, Folder 490)
    - New York State Publishers Association, 1967 September 25 (Box 72, Folder 491)
    - Public Relations Society of America, 1967 September 28 (Box 72, Folder 492)
    - Auxiliary Police Force, 1967 September 28 (Box 72, Folder 493)
    - New York-Ontario Shrine Association, 1967 September 29 (Box 72, Folder 494)
    - National Association for Advancement of Colored people, 1967 September 29 (Box 72, Folder 495)
    - Teachers' strike, 1967 October 1 (Box 72, Folder 496)
    - The New York Cultural Showcase Foundation (Whitney Museum), 1967 October 1 (Box 72, Folder 497)
    - The New York Cultural Showcase Foundation, 1967 October 2 (Box 72, Folder 498)
    - The New York Cultural Showcase Foundation (Brooklyn Museum), 1967 October 3 (Box 72, Folder 499)
    - The New York Cultural Showcase Foundation (Cooper Union Museum), 1967 October 5 (Box 72, Folder 500)
    - New York State AFL-CIO, 1967 October 2 (Box 72, Folder 501)
    - United Hospital Fund of New York, 1967 October 2, 3 (Box 72, Folder 502-503)
    - Water Pollution Control Federation, 1967 October 9 (Box 72, Folder 504)
    - South Bronx Concentrated Employment Program (Box 73, Folder 505)
    - New York State Bankers Association, 1967 October 9 (Box 73, Folder 506)
    - Fire Department of the City of New York, essay awards, 1967 October 10 (Box 73, Folder 507)
    - "Salute to Fall", 1967 October 10 (Box 73, Folder 508)
    - The New York Showcase Foundation (jewish museum), 1967 October 10 (Box 73, Folder 509)
    - Columbus Citizens Committee, Inc., 1967 October 10 (Box 73, Folder 510)
    - Liberal party of New York state, 1967 October 11 (Box 73, Folder 511)
    - New York City Central Labor Council AFL-CIO, 1967 October 19 (Box 73, Folder 512)
    - St. Paul's Cathedral, Buffalo, New York, 1967 October 19 (Box 73, Folder 513)
    - John Foster Dulles Republican Club, 1967 October 20 (Box 73, Folder 514)
    - Greek Orthodox Archdiocese of North and South America, 1967 October 22 (Box 73, Folder 515)
    - Statement re: proposed new state constitution, 1967 October 23 (Box 73, Folder 516)
    - Pratt Institute, 1967 October 23 (Box 73, Folder 517)
    - New York Board of Trade, Business Speaks dinner, 1967 October 24 (Box 73, Folder 518)
    - Regional Air Pollution Conference, 1967 October 25 (Box 73, Folder 519)
    - Catholic Settlement Association, 1967 October 25 (Box 73, Folder 520)
    - Harvard Business School Club of New York, 1967 October 26 (Box 73, Folder 521)
    - Pace College, 1967 October 26 (Box 73, Folder 522)
    - Duveen Soap Corporation (costello), 1967 October 26 (Box 73, Folder 523)
    - Brooklyn College, 1967 October 27 (Box 73, Folder 524)
    - John Foster Dulles Republican Club, 1967 October 27 (Box 73, Folder 525)
    - Fact Finding Committee of Entertainment Unions, 1967 October 27 (Box 73, Folder 526)
    - Adali E. Stevenson Democratic Club, 1967 October 27 (Box 73, Folder 527)
    - Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1967 October 30 (Box 73, Folder 528)
    - Business salutes city center, 1967 October 30 (Box 73, Folder 529)
    - Altro Health and Rehabilitation Service, 1967 November 1 (Box 73, Folder 530)
    - The One - Hundred Men, Inc., 1967 November 1 (Box 73, Folder 531)
    - The Association of the Bar of New York, 1967 November 6 (Box 73, Folder 532)
    - Citizens for Clean Air, 1967 November 6 (Box 73, Folder 533)
    - Jamica Chamber of Commerce, 1967 November 6 (Box 73, Folder 534)
    - Four Freedoms Foundation, 1967 November 8 (Box 73, Folder 535)
    - Labor Human Rights awards dinner, 1967 November 9 (Box 73, Folder 536)
    - Queensborough Community College, 1967 November 13 (Box 73, Folder 537)
    - Staten Island Chamber of Commerce, 1967 November 13 (Box 73, Folder 538)
    - Commerce and Industry Association of New York, 1967 November 14 (Box 74, Folder 539)
    - Proposed gun control law, public hearings, 1967 November 14 (Box 74, Folder 540)